I'm here in the UK at Penguin which I love because
I think Penguin is the best publisher in the world
and England is the center of the English language.
And that's quite a bit because
England has brought a tradition to the world
of truth-finding and clarification
and illuminated it in various ways
and I hope this book
that takes English tradition a step further
as befits a good settler.
So
I hope you read it
and I hope it helps put your life in order.
I think people like the things I've said
very helpful in that area
and I have tried to clear them
and expand with this book
to deepen them.
So hopefully you will find out when you read it.